<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>①ne is 3 (migrated_from_tumblr)</title><link>http://oneis3.com</link><description>One is 3</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 01:41:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>nikola</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Python Script to download Splunk Documentation PDFs</title><link>http://oneis3.com/posts/python-script-to-download-splunk-documentation-pdfs.html</link><description>&lt;head&gt;&lt;script src="https://gist.github.com/4121269.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/head&gt;</description><guid>http://oneis3.com/posts/python-script-to-download-splunk-documentation-pdfs.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 16:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Open in SourceTree from IntelliJ IDEA</title><link>http://oneis3.com/posts/open-in-sourcetree-from-intellij-idea.html</link><description>&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm quite fond of &lt;a href="http://www.sourcetreeapp.com/"&gt;SourceTree&lt;/a&gt; for managing Git repositories (it does Mercurial as well).  SourceTree comes with an &lt;code&gt;stree&lt;/code&gt; command to open repositories from the command line.  I wanted to set up an &lt;a href="http://www.jetbrains.com/idea/webhelp/external-tools.html"&gt;external tool in IntelliJ IDEA&lt;/a&gt; to the repo containing the current source file, &lt;code&gt;stree&lt;/code&gt; only works if you call it without any arguments with a current working directory of the root level of a repo, or if you pass the path to the root level of a repo as an argument.  This is fine if you have only a single Git source root in your IntelliJ project:  You can just use call &lt;code&gt;stree&lt;/code&gt; directly with the &lt;code&gt;$ProjectFileDir$&lt;/code&gt; macro as a parameter.  But if you have multiple modules in your project with different Git source roots, it gets more difficult.  I tried using the &lt;code&gt;$ModuleFileDir$&lt;/code&gt; macro, but this seems to the directory where the &lt;code&gt;.iml&lt;/code&gt; file for the module is stored, which is not the source root of the module.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I ended up writing a small wrapper for &lt;code&gt;stree&lt;/code&gt; which can take the path to any file or directory within a Git or Mercurial repo as an argument and invokes &lt;code&gt;stree&lt;/code&gt; with the path to the root of the repo:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script src="https://gist.github.com/3051104.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><guid>http://oneis3.com/posts/open-in-sourcetree-from-intellij-idea.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 12:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>